Man, I'm glad I got this opportunity. I
can't wait. I'm I'm ready to get to
work. Send me the playbook right now.
>> What do you think you can What do you
think you can add here,
>> man? I I feel like um I'm going be a
great competitor like in the room. Um
bring everybody along and just, you
know, be ready to work. I'm ready to get
to work right now. Um I feel like I'm a
competitor and me being in the room, I
feel like it's going to make everybody
better for sure. And I just can't wait
to join Washington, man. It's close to
the crib. I can't wait, man. is it's a
blessing, man. Can't you feel? I don't
even got to It's a blessing, though.
>> Did you grow up as a Washington fan?
>> No, I didn't, but it's close to the
crib. I'm a fan now.
>> K, I know you also have basketball in
your background. Is there anything you
kind of transfer from that sport into
your your style of playing football?
>> Um, yeah. I feel like um just dribbling
the ball and stuff like that, the way I
move um feel like it kind of contributes
to me playing basketball. Um it's kind
of familiar like the moves and stuff,
how you move. It just you don't got a
ball. You don't got a basketball, you
got a football in your hand. So I feel
like me playing basketball, it played a
big part in me how I play running back.
I just feel like people don't that's my
people don't understand like that's the
under they underestimate that that I can
move and stuff like that. So man, I'm
happy man. I'm excited, man. for sure.
>> What's your strength as a runner, do you
think?
>> Man, I feel like I can do everything as
a running back. Feel like people don't
like people don't respect it enough. Um,
but I feel like I can scrim, toughness,
phys physicality, everything. I put
everything into a running back that you
need in a running back. I feel like I do
that well and it's go it's going to be
on full display and I'm ready to go
right now, man. I'm ready to play right
now. Put the rock in my hands. I'm ready
to go scope.
>> You said that having you on this team is
going to make everybody better. Could
you elaborate on that a little bit more?
>> I just feel like um when players around
me, man, they got no no other choice but
to get better around me. Um just because
my work ethic and how I go about playing
football, I love football. So, I put
everything into it and you know, and I
just feel like you're around me, you got
to love football or if not, it's going
to show. But man, I'm a great team guy,
man. I just can't get wait to get there
and get ready to get to work and stuff
like that, man. I'm ready. Did you talk
to these guys much or were you were you
surprised to come here or
>> man? No, I don't. But man, I'm just
blessed with the opportunity. I'm just
ready to get to work and I'm ready to
play ball. What I love to do, I'm a
football player and you gonna see it's
going to be on full display.
>> Bill Crosky Merritt was a seventh round
pick here last year. Had a lot of
success as a running back, as a rookie.
>> Uh how do you feel about landing in in a
place that trusted a late round pick,
rookie running back, and the opportunity
you might have this year? U they man I
feel like if they draft me they um you
know that mean they they want me to come
there and do something special and I'm
ready for it I'm ready for the challenge
and you know I'm ready to get to work
man and you know I'm a great team guy
team you feel me like I said before man
I make everybody around me better
football defense offense special team it
don't matter what it is organization I'm
make everybody around me get better
>> how do you feel about joining a team
with Jaden Daniels at quarterback
>> it's crazy man he's special man I can't
wait to be in the same backfield as And
you know, it's gonna be it's gonna be
something special, man, that people
don't, you feel me, underestimate. And
I'm ready to get to work, man. Just I
say, man, put the ball in my hands. I'm
ready to go right now.
>> Hey, you you faced Sunny Styles in
college. What did you think about him as
a linebacker?
>> He a great linebacker, man. Um, he
determined. He love football, too. And
just his work ethic, and you know, he a
great football player, and I just can't
wait to go against him and compete and
get better every day, make him better,
and he made me better.
>> Kron, can you talk about your nickname?
And and do you prefer to go by your
nickname or do you prefer Kron?
>> I prefer fat man. Um that's my that's my
nickname my mom gave me when I was a
jit. Um I was a fat baby and everybody
in the town called me fat man and
hopefully I keep it going in they call
me fat man and you know when I score all
you heard is fat, you feel me? It's
going to be something. It gonna be
special man. I can't wait.
>> I know ball security is a big part of
your game. How proud are you of that
fact?
>> Man, I'm proud of it. You feel me? I
take great pride in it because you got
everybody dreams and aspiration in your
hand. So I take great pride in it and
you know that's something I I can't you
feel me I won't do and I you feel me
take pride in not doing turnovers you
stuff that's not who I am and football I
take great care because I love football
and I don't want nobody else taking my
dream aspiration away.
>> Do you think you have another level to
show as a pass catcher compared to what
you did at Penn State?
>> Man I can't wait to show up man. I feel
like people ain't underestimate that
too. And you know, I'm a great I can run
routes, get open, stuff like that. And
they going to see, man. I feel like
where I was at, it ain't I ain't show
everything that I needed to show, but
they going to see.
>> Thank you.
>> Appreciate you. Yeah. Appreciate your
time.